[
    {
        "question": "What is the city of Brotherly Love?",
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country covers an entire continent?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What western US city is dubbed \u201cThe Valley of 10,000 Buffets\u201d?",
        "answer": "Las Vegas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What 4 seas are named for colors?",
        "answer": "Red, White, Yellow and Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Caribbean island of Aruba is part of what European kingdom?",
        "answer": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Ring of Fire surround?",
        "answer": "Pacific Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only state that borders more than two Canadian provinces?",
        "answer": "Montana -- The Treasure State has British Columbia, Alberta, and Saskatchewan as its neighbors to the north."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the eight major islands in Hawaii has no permanent residents?",
        "answer": "Kaho`olawe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country has the largest tar pit?",
        "answer": "Trinidad and Tobago"
    },
    {
        "question": "Willapa Bay opens into what body of water?",
        "answer": "Pacific Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Darjeeling tea grown?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Iraq?",
        "answer": "Baghdad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paramaribo is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Suriname"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paramaribo is the capital of which South American country?",
        "answer": "Suriname"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Suriname gain its independence from the Kingdom of the Netherlands?",
        "answer": "1975"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American country`s name is literally `Land of Silver`",
        "answer": "Argentina`s"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which ocean are the Seychelles?",
        "answer": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Ellora Caves are located in which Asian country?",
        "answer": "India -- The Ellora Caves in India are home to 34 remarkable, rock-hewn temples."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the largest outdoor rodeo held in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Cheyenne, Wyoming -- Cheyenne`s Frontier Days is an outdoor rodeo and western celebration that attracts 200,000 people each year."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which couple is credited with forming the nation of Spain?",
        "answer": "Ferdinand II of Aragon and Isabella O of Castile"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country was a method for making rust-resistant iron discovered in the fifth century B.C.?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "What creature do the Galapagos Islands take their name from?",
        "answer": "Tortoise"
    },
    {
        "question": "The `Chuuk Lagoon`, considered one of the best World War II wreck dive sites, is part of which island nation?",
        "answer": "Micronesia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Popular in the Balkans, what type of beverage is the `Rakia`?",
        "answer": "Fruit brandy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which stretch of water seperates Tierra del Fuego from the rest of South America?",
        "answer": "Strait of Magellan"
    },
    {
        "question": "The `Strait of Magellan` is part of which continent?",
        "answer": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent would you find the `Strait of Magellan` in?",
        "answer": "South America"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Plains of Abraham are located in which country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state was named after a president?",
        "answer": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "What larger park is found in Manhattan?",
        "answer": "Central Park"
    },
    {
        "question": "The zip code 90210 is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the residents of Florida called?",
        "answer": "Floridians"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s two letter postal abbreviation is `MD`?",
        "answer": "Maryland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the westernmost state in the US?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows through Jackson Hole, Wyoming?",
        "answer": "The Snake River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What language do natives call Farsi?",
        "answer": "Persian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cuisine gave us kimchi and bulgogi?",
        "answer": "Korean"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano `Etna`?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the active volcano `Lassen Peak`?",
        "answer": "The United States"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the world`s largest parking lot?",
        "answer": "West Edmonton Mall, Edmonton, AB, Canada -- It will serve 20,000 cars at the world`s second largest shopping mall."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which countries does Bangladesh share a land border with?",
        "answer": "India and Myanmar (Burma)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Falcon State is located in which South American country?",
        "answer": "Venezuela"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state has the largest aquifer?",
        "answer": "Nebraska"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Amazon river?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the Volga river?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the mouths of the river Nile?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are the Mayan ruins of Tikal located?",
        "answer": "Guatemala"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you find the `Dancing House`?",
        "answer": "Prague, Czech Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you drive the `Extraterrestrial Highway`?",
        "answer": "Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dover is the capital of which US state?",
        "answer": "Delaware"
    }
]